formula_questions = [
    {
        "question": "The year is 2004, \
and the driver is Michael Schumacher. Name the team mate?:",
        "options": ["Felipe Massa", "Rubens Barrichello"],
        "correct": "Rubens Barrichello"
    },
    {
        "question": "Back to 1986 now. Who was Ayrton Senna's \
team mate at Team Lotus?:",
        "options": ["Johnny Dumfries", "Mika HÃ¤kkinen"],
        "correct": "Johnny Dumfries"
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was Max Verstappen's team mate at \
Toro Rosso in 2015? ",
        "options": ["Danill Kvyat", "Carlos Sainz"],
        "correct": "Carlos Sainz"
    },
    {
        "question": "Lewis Hamilton won his first Formula 1 \
World Championship in 2008, but by how many points?",
        "options": ["3 points", "1 points"],
        "correct": "1 points"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these drivers was youngest when \
they clinched their second Formula 1 World Championship?",
        "options": ["Sebastian Vettel", "Lewis Hamilton"],
        "correct": "Sebastian Vettel"
    },
    {
        "question": "Hamilton took his first Grand Slam, pole position, \
win, and every lap led. In what Grand Prix of 2014?",
        "options": ["Malaysia", "Monza"],
        "correct": "Malaysia"
    },
    {
        "question": "At which Grand Prix did Hamilton secure the 2015 title?",
        "options": ["USA", "Bahrain"],
        "correct": "USA"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which driver suffered the most retirements (DNFs) \
in the 2020 season?",
        "options": ["Kevin Magnussen", "Lance Stroll"],
        "correct": "Kevin Magnussen"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which driver raced the most laps in 2020?",
        "options": ["Lando Norris", "Lewis Hamilton"],
        "correct": "Lando Norris"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these races had the fewest \
classified finishers in 2020?",
        "options": ["British Grand Prix", "Tuscan Grand Prix"],
        "correct": "Tuscan Grand Prix"
    },
    {
        "question": "Daniel Ricciardo paid tribute to which of these \
persons with a special helmet in 2020?",
        "options": ["Kobe Bryant", "Diego Maradona"],
        "correct": "Kobe Bryant"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which year was the first ever official \
formula one race?",
        "options": ["1948", "1950"],
        "correct": "1950"
    }
]
